http://www.bsueboutiques.com/terms_privacy.asp

Skip to content
Automatic Free Shipping on U.S. orders over $50.00 (after coupon use)
Search site:
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature.When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes. it is 100% NEVER shared with ANYONE, EVER.
And all of your information is PROTECTED under the most stringent of measures.
NONE of your information is stored in our office in separate files.
What we have is what you have given us to fill your order, and placed in our care when you made an account.
Just simple things, like name, address, phone number.
The IP address does come up for security reasons.
Beyond that, we don't have anything about you in our files and we never see your credit card number.
We process with AuthorizeNet, one of the largest and most prestigious merchant processors in the US.
And, of course, we process with PayPal.
Both are completely compliant with GDPR standards as well as our own security standards.
You will also see that our site carries an SSL badge.
This is a guarantee to you that this is a SAFE site, and that your basic data collected so that we can ship you your orders, is kept in the most careful confidence.
You can click on it and get our address and phone number and current compliance rating, at any time.Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
These cookies are part of the Volusion platform, the platform under which we are housed.
The cookies are applied through their system and have not been programmed into this website by us.
If you do not want websites to collect basic things via cookies, please take responsibility to disable them on your computer.....knowing that if you do, your internet experience could be less satisfactory, not just here at our website, but just about everywhere you go.
Cookies are very standard and they actually make your internet surfing and shopping more enjoyable!How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.To quickly process your transactions.To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails.
YOUR NAME IS NEVER EVER PLACED ON AN EMAIL LIST BY US.
It would only be there if you placed it there. It is entirely unethical for companies to gather names or put you on a list if you have not requested it. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below.
ALSO:
EVERY EMAIL HAS AN EASY UNSUB LINK, and it works great!
So if the emails are too much or you don't want to get them anymore, just click it....and you will not get them any longer. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.How do we protect visitor information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. Our employees are all trained in this type of security.
When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.Do we use "cookies"?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These cookies are such as Google Analytics, Full Story, CallRail, Intercom,Pardot, FirstParty, Optimizely, Marketo, MaxMind. These are quite commonly used by most reliable websites these days.
These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
PLEASE KNOW:
If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include www.bsueboutiques.com. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. NOTE:
as mentioned, this information would not identify you personally. How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.Third party linksIn an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).Changes to our policyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on May 24, 2018.Questions and feedbackWe welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.
YOU MAY ABSOLUTELY ask for your information to be disposed of, deleted, etc from our system.
You may also PERSONALLY update your own information in your customer account.
Customers can easily request that we not process an order by contacting Jordan at jordan@bsueboutiques.com
You data can be delivered to you if you request it.
You may again request deletion of your data at any time. If our policies here regarding your privacy are ever updated, you will be informed promptly.
AGAIN:
all of our employees are carefully trained about the value and integrity of your privacy.
Our website upholds the highest security, along with our third party processors, Authorize NET and PayPal.
WE NEVER SEE YOUR CREDIT CARD NUMBER when your order is processed and we do not have it on file.
We regularly review our polices for changes in data handling here in the US as well as EU and all other international countries we deal with.
Data
is not transferred from EU or anywhere inside the US or outside
except under the highest level of protection.
Online Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline by a third party.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.Your consentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. Again, our technical security is the finest and up to date, and you may check the SSL certificate to confirm it.
